<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Giovanni Marigi - Personal Page</title>
    <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Giovanni Marigi - Personal Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://hifly81.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>But long enough to bloom</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/jamiroquai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/jamiroquai/</guid>
      <description>I know all the songs of two bands: The Beach Boys and Jamiroquai.
I grew up with the former&amp;rsquo;s vinyl records at home and I have always found their music to be a work of art of virtuosity and creativity. And then I discovered the music of Jamiroquai in my teenage years.
In many ways I have always compared them to The Beach Boys, for their musical experimentation, for the joy of their melodies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ma che discorsi</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/machediscorsi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/machediscorsi/</guid>
      <description>Se pensi che sia logico Scoprire in mezzo al traffico Di amarsi in modo cosmico Ma un attimo che poi due metri dopo L&amp;rsquo;amore sembra consumato già
Lo so che non ti piacciono Le situazioni in bilico Le cose che succedono E succedono lo so Ma che discorsi Sei tu che butti sempre tutto giù Ma che discorsi Nel dubbio che poi non funzioni più Così fai tu.
E poi con quello che succede In una storia come questa Non è che ti può chiedere Se sia la strada giusta Ad ogni angolo, ogni semaforo che c&amp;rsquo;è</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Napoleon</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/napoleon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/napoleon/</guid>
      <description>Warning [SPOILER ALERT]
I recently saw Ridley Scott&amp;rsquo;s new film, Napoleon, a short cinematic reconstruction of the rise and fall of Napoleon Bonaparte.
Napoleon is played by Joaquin Phoenix, an outstanding actor in every performance. Even if here in my opinion a little subdued.
The film retraces some of the most important battles of Bonaparte&amp;rsquo;s career and is centered on the love story with his Josephine. There are some scenes that are a little rough in my opinion, not worthy of Ridley Scott (the cannons against the Egyptian pyramids?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NAZ, rise and fall of Prince Naseem Hamed</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/naz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/naz/</guid>
      <description>At the suggestion of a friend of mine, I saw a short documentary on the boxing career of Prince Naseem Hamed.
&amp;ldquo;Naz&amp;rdquo; was certainly one of the most influential boxers of the late 90s and early 2000s and one of the greatest featherweights in history. He had very powerful and precise strikes for a featherweight and an engaging, very show-oriented in-ring style.
I have always had the idea that his successful career was made possible by having to face weak opponents and by the need to create a character who could bring prestige to the minor categories of boxing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NBA In-Season Tournament</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/nba-inseason/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/nba-inseason/</guid>
      <description>A tournament within the already exhausting NBA season.
It&amp;rsquo;s called the NBA In-Season Tournament which this week will see the final round and the winner of the first edition.
The prize will be a cash budget to be distributed to the various players and the new trophy, NBA Cup (a kind of National Cup?).
Luckily the matches of this new tournament will also be valid for the regular season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street of Philadelphia</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/street-of-philadelphia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/street-of-philadelphia/</guid>
      <description>Some days ago like every year, December 1st, was International AIDS Day.
The AIDS syndrome appeared forcefully in the 1980s and is still a very important and widespread disease today.
There is very little communication now on this topic but it is good to remember that 40 years later, medicine has made important progress and today people with the HIV virus live an almost normal life. Yes, because the HIV virus leads to AIDS syndrome only if patients do not adequately follow a therapeutic path and do not take drugs that contain the virus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The great dictator - Final speech</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/great-dictator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/great-dictator/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, but I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be an emperor That&amp;rsquo;s not my business I don&amp;rsquo;t want to rule or conquer anyone I should like to help everyone if possible Jew, Gentile, Black Man, White We all want to help one another, human beings are like that We want to live by each other&amp;rsquo;s happiness, not by each other&amp;rsquo;s misery We don&amp;rsquo;t want to hate and despise one another
And this world has room for everyone, and the good Earth is rich and can provide for everyone The way of life can be free and beautiful, but we have lost the way Greed has posioned men&amp;rsquo;s souls, has barricaded the world with hate, has goose-stepped us into misery and bloodshed We have developed speed, but we have shut ourselves in Machinery that gives us abundance has left us in want</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The importance of reading books</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>At the basis of a simple and natural understanding of oneself, which is I believe the definition of happiness (albeit intermittently), is the discovery of what is not so obvious through reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The unbearable lightness of being REM</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/all-the-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/all-the-way/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a reason why I like REM&amp;rsquo;s songs, because they are ethereal and have a dreamlike dimension for me.
One big regret is never having seen them live. They&amp;rsquo;re certainly not the type to do a nostalgic reunion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tyson vs Douglas</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/tyson-douglas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/tyson-douglas/</guid>
      <description>My father was a great boxing fan and inevitably passed this passion on to me too.
I saw many matches with him, especially those of Carlos Monzon and Marvin &amp;ldquo;The Marvelous&amp;rdquo; Hagler.
In the second half of the 80s the heavyweight scene was monopolized by a boy from the suburbs of New York, who became the youngest heavyweight champion of the world, Mike &amp;ldquo;Iron&amp;rdquo; Tyson, shocking the world with instant KOs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
