<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Giovanni Marigi - Personal Page</title>
    <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Giovanni Marigi - Personal Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://hifly81.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>All the way</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/all-the-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/all-the-way/</guid>
      <description>to Reno, to anywhere&amp;hellip; There&amp;rsquo;s a reason why I like REM&amp;rsquo;s songs, because they are ethereal and have a dreamlike dimension for me.
One big regret is never having seen them live. They&amp;rsquo;re certainly not the type to do a nostalgic reunion</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dirty Dancing</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/dirty_dancing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/dirty_dancing/</guid>
      <description>Last night after many years I happened to see Dirty Dancing again, a film I think everyone knows.
The intensity of some scenes in this film are so current that seeing them again I was left speechless as always. And the message of love without limits, impossible but then possible is a timeless classic.
It is also a tribute to a great actor like Patrick Swayze who always gave me the idea of being a person with kind and polite ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hanno ucciso l&#39;uomo ragno</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/hanno-ucciso-luomo-ragno/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/hanno-ucciso-luomo-ragno/</guid>
      <description>Solita notte da lupi nel Bronx Nel locale stan suonando un blues degli Stones Loschi individui al bancone del bar Pieni di whisky e margaritas
Tutto ad un tratto la porta fa slam Il guercio entra di corsa con una novità Dritta sicura: si mormora che I cannoni hanno fatto bang
Hanno ucciso l&amp;rsquo;Uomo Ragno, chi sia stato non si sa Forse quelli della mala, forse la pubblicità Hanno ucciso l&amp;rsquo;Uomo Ragno, non si sa neanche il perché Avrà fatto qualche sgarro a qualche industria di caffè</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Napoleon</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/napoleon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/napoleon/</guid>
      <description>Warning [SPOILER ALERT]
I recently saw Ridley Scott&amp;rsquo;s new film, Napoleon, a short cinematic reconstruction of the rise and fall of Napoleon Bonaparte.
Napoleon is played by Joaquin Phoenix, an outstanding actor in every performance. Even if here in my opinion a little subdued.
The film retraces some of the most important battles of Bonaparte&amp;rsquo;s career and is centered on the love story with his Josephine. There are some scenes that are a little rough in my opinion, not worthy of Ridley Scott (the cannons against the Egyptian pyramids?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street of Philadelphia</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/street-of-philadelphia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/street-of-philadelphia/</guid>
      <description>Some days like every year, December 1st was International AIDS Day.
The AIDS syndrome appeared forcefully in the 1980s and is still a very important and widespread disease today.
There is very little communication now on this topic but it is good to remember that 40 years later, medicine has made important progress and today people with the HIV virus live an almost normal life. Yes, because the HIV virus leads to AIDS syndrome only if patients do not adequately follow a therapeutic path and do not take drugs that contain the virus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The great dictator - Final speech</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/great-dictator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/great-dictator/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, but I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be an emperor That&amp;rsquo;s not my business I don&amp;rsquo;t want to rule or conquer anyone I should like to help everyone if possible Jew, Gentile, Black Man, White We all want to help one another, human beings are like that We want to live by each other&amp;rsquo;s happiness, not by each other&amp;rsquo;s misery We don&amp;rsquo;t want to hate and despise one another
And this world has room for everyone, and the good Earth is rich and can provide for everyone The way of life can be free and beautiful, but we have lost the way Greed has posioned men&amp;rsquo;s souls, has barricaded the world with hate, has goose-stepped us into misery and bloodshed We have developed speed, but we have shut ourselves in Machinery that gives us abundance has left us in want</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The importance of reading books</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>At the basis of a simple and natural understanding of oneself, which is I believe the definition of happiness (albeit intermittently), is the discovery of what is not so obvious through reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tyson vs Douglas</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/tyson-douglas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/tyson-douglas/</guid>
      <description>My father was a great boxing fan and inevitably passed this passion on to me too.
I saw many matches with him before I was born, especially those of Monzon and Marvin &amp;ldquo;The Marvelous&amp;rdquo; Hagler.
In the second half of the 80s the heavyweight scene was monopolized by a boy from the suburbs of New York, who became the youngest heavyweight champion of the world, Mike &amp;ldquo;Iron&amp;rdquo; Tyson, by dint of instant KOs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
