<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Giovanni Marigi - Personal Page</title>
    <link>https://hifly81.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Giovanni Marigi - Personal Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 08:55:49 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hifly81.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dirty Dancing</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/dirty_dancing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 08:55:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/dirty_dancing/</guid>
      <description>Last night after many years I happened to see Dirty Dancing again, a film I think everyone knows.
The intensity of some scenes in this film are so current that seeing them again I was left speechless as always. And the message of love without limits, impossible but then possible is a timeless classic.
It is also a tribute to a great actor like Patrick Swayze who always gave me the idea of being a person with kind and polite ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The importance of reading books</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:55:49 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>At the basis of a simple and natural understanding of oneself, which is I believe the definition of happiness (albeit intermittently), is the discovery of what is not so obvious through reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a guy (and always will be in spirit) over 40 who works as a Solutions Architects in the IT sector.
I studied Computer Engineering and my background is humanistic and the subjects studied during my high school years have remained my passions as can be seen in this website.
In addition to literature, the study of history, art and music, I have a great passion for sport in general and mainly follow and practice mountain biking, trekking, tennis, swimming and basketball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/art/</guid>
      <description>Jean-Michel Basquiat Warrior painting, 1982 Vincent Van Gogh Prisoners Exercising , also known as Prisoners&amp;rsquo; Round , (After Gustave Doré) oil on canvas, 1890, Pushkin State Museum of Fine Arts, Moscow, Russia </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/books/</guid>
      <description> Into the Wild - Jon Krakauer A long walk to freedom - Nelson Mandela Una persona alla volta - Gino Strada Who moved my cheese? - Spencer Johnson </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/food/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/food/</guid>
      <description> Spaghetti alle vongole Chateau Gazin-Rocquencourt - Pessac-Léognan Blanc 2018 Banana split Aperol Spritz Dry Martini Capesante gratinate Fritto misto di pesce Tonnarelli alla carbonara </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/fun/</guid>
      <description> Are you the one? Un baffo del genere in Italia fai fatica a vederlo Calvo Io canto da solo Il castello della sobrietà Cinque ragazzi per me La dolce Chiara Daniele e la sua EX Glauco - Boris 2 L&amp;rsquo;insostenibile leggerezza dell&amp;rsquo;essere Matrimonio al sud Noci di cocco Provini X Factor Renè contro gli avvocati - Boris Il ritorno di Sasha San Ceppato Scuola di giornalismo Il segreto del successo Se il mare fosse de tocio Sossoldi Talenti incompresi A tratti Il vecchio conio La vita è tutto un quiz </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/misc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/misc/</guid>
      <description> Vespa 50 SPECIAL ELESTART (V5A3T) - 1973 Jeep Renegade Kross Level B12 - 2017 Ford Focus RS Volvo V40 D2 R-design </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/movie/</guid>
      <description> Deutschland 83 Dirty Dancing Full Metal Jacket Inglorious Bastards Into the Wild The Last Dance MAP1MP1: The Makazole Mapimpi Story The Prestige Schindler&amp;rsquo;s List Scene da un matrimonio The Usual Suspects </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/sport/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/sport/</guid>
      <description> Diego Milito scores 1-0 | Inter vs Bayern Munich Uefa Champions League 2010 Fabio Grosso Goal vs Germany | World Cup 2006 Jannik Sinner cancels three match points from Novak Djokovic | Davis Cup Semifinal 2023 Top Ten Magic Johnson plays </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
