<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Giovanni Marigi - Personal Page</title>
    <link>https://hifly81.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Giovanni Marigi - Personal Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://hifly81.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am over 40, and I&amp;rsquo;m currently working as a Solutions Architects in the IT sector.
I studied Computer Engineering and my background is humanistic and the subjects studied during my high school years have remained my passions as can be seen in this website.
In addition to literature, the study of history, art and music, I have a great passion for sport in general and mainly follow and practice mountain biking, trekking, tennis, swimming and basketball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/aid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/aid/</guid>
      <description>Emergency
Save the children
UNHCR
Unicef</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/art/</guid>
      <description>Tiziano Amor Sacro e Amor Profano oil on canvas, 1514, Galleria Borghese, Rome, Italy Jean-Michel Basquiat Warrior painting, 1982 Vincent Van Gogh Prisoners Exercising , also known as Prisoners&amp;rsquo; Round , (After Gustave Doré) oil on canvas, 1890, Pushkin State Museum of Fine Arts, Moscow, Russia Michelangelo La pietà marble sculpture, 1497-1499, Basilica di San Pietro, Città del Vaticano </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/books/</guid>
      <description> Into the Wild - Jon Krakauer A long walk to freedom - Nelson Mandela Una persona alla volta - Gino Strada Who moved my cheese? - Spencer Johnson </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/food/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/food/</guid>
      <description> Spaghetti alle vongole Chateau Gazin-Rocquencourt - Pessac-Léognan Blanc 2018 Banana split Aperol Spritz Dry Martini Capesante gratinate Fritto misto di pesce Tonnarelli alla carbonara Ciobar Pancakes </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/fun/</guid>
      <description> Are you the one? Un baffo del genere in Italia fai fatica a vederlo Calvo Io canto da solo Il castello della sobrietà Cinque ragazzi per me La dolce Chiara Corrado Guzzanti è Mariano Giusti Daniele e la sua EX Glauco - Boris 2 L&amp;rsquo;insostenibile leggerezza dell&amp;rsquo;essere Matrimonio al sud Mr. Flanagan e Rolando Nico e i sardi Noci di cocco Provini X Factor Renè contro gli avvocati - Boris Il ritorno di Sasha San Ceppato Scuola di giornalismo Il segreto del successo Se il mare fosse de tocio Sossoldi Talenti incompresi A tratti Il vecchio conio La vita è tutto un quiz </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/misc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/misc/</guid>
      <description> Vespa 50 SPECIAL ELESTART (V5A3T) - 1973 Jeep Renegade Kross Level B12 - 2017 Ford Focus RS Volvo V40 D2 R-design Audi RS3 Sportback Subaru Impreza WRX STI Kawasaki Ninja 650 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/movie/</guid>
      <description> 12 anni schiavo A beatiful mind Back to the future Big fish Deutschland 83 Dirty Dancing Catch me if you can Full Metal Jacket Inglorious Bastards Into the Wild Jurassic Park La La Land The Last Dance Matrix MAP1MP1: The Makazole Mapimpi Story Million Dollar Baby The Prestige Pulp Fiction Rush Schindler&amp;rsquo;s List Scene da un matrimonio Silicon Valley The Usual Suspects Total Recall 1990 Whiplash The Wolf of Wall Street </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Groups of which I am a member and whose activities I support:
Roma Apache Kafka® Meetup by Confluent
Milano Apache Kafka® Meetup by Confluent
Golang Roma
This is a list of the main projects I contribute to. See the complete list on my github repo: https://github.com/hifly81
JR streaming quality random data from the command line https://github.com/ugol/jr Confluent JMX monitoring stacks Monitoring examples for Confluent Cloud and Confluent Platform https://github.com/confluentinc/jmx-monitoring-stacks kafka-examples Practical examples with Apache Kafka® https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/sport/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/sport/</guid>
      <description> Diego Milito scores 1-0 | Inter vs Bayern Munich Uefa Champions League 2010 Fabio Grosso Goal vs Germany | World Cup 2006 Jannik Sinner cancels three match points from Novak Djokovic | Davis Cup Semifinal 2023 Top Ten Magic Johnson plays </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>But long enough to bloom</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/jamiroquai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/jamiroquai/</guid>
      <description>I know all the songs of two bands: The Beach Boys and Jamiroquai.
I grew up with the former&amp;rsquo;s vinyl records at home and I have always found their music to be a work of art of virtuosity and creativity. And then I discovered the music of Jamiroquai in my teenage years.
In many ways I have always compared them to The Beach Boys, for their musical experimentation, for the joy of their melodies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City of stars</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/cityofstarts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/cityofstarts/</guid>
      <description>City of stars Are you shining just for me? City of stars There&amp;rsquo;s so much that I can&amp;rsquo;t see Who knows? I felt it from the first embrace I shared with you That now our dreams They&amp;rsquo;ve finally come true
City of stars Just one thing everybody wants There in the bars And through the smokescreen of the crowded restaurants
It&amp;rsquo;s love Yes, all we&amp;rsquo;re looking for is love from someone else</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discolabirinto</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/discolabirinto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/discolabirinto/</guid>
      <description>Quasi quasi lo farei Quasi quasi dimmelo Quasi quasi ti ho tradito E mi sono divertito
Quasi quasi non ti ascolto Quasi quasi ho il vomito Quasi quasi esagero Se mi sopravvaluto
Vorrei una discoteca labirinto Bianca senza luci colorate Grande un centinaio di chilometri Dalla quale non si possa uscire
Vorrei una discoteca labirinto Bianca senza luci colorate Grande un centinaio di chilometri Dalla quale non si possa uscire</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discolabirinto</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/kingforaday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/kingforaday/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s no way I&amp;rsquo;m coming back to you I&amp;rsquo;ve just got to say That everything we did is through You tried to undermine The better ranges of my nature But soon you&amp;rsquo;re going to find You should have started talking straighter Now don&amp;rsquo;t you worry I won&amp;rsquo;t put you down I&amp;rsquo;m in no hurry, baby To see you go to ground Because it&amp;rsquo;s true what they say You know it&amp;rsquo;s true what they say You&amp;rsquo;re only king for a day I guess you&amp;rsquo;re happy that way</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ma che discorsi</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/machediscorsi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/machediscorsi/</guid>
      <description>Se pensi che sia logico Scoprire in mezzo al traffico Di amarsi in modo cosmico Ma un attimo che poi due metri dopo L&amp;rsquo;amore sembra consumato già
Lo so che non ti piacciono Le situazioni in bilico Le cose che succedono E succedono lo so Ma che discorsi Sei tu che butti sempre tutto giù Ma che discorsi Nel dubbio che poi non funzioni più Così fai tu.
E poi con quello che succede In una storia come questa Non è che ti può chiedere Se sia la strada giusta Ad ogni angolo, ogni semaforo che c&amp;rsquo;è</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mediterraneo conteso</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/mediterraneo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/mediterraneo/</guid>
      <description>Ho partecipato all&amp;rsquo;annuale fiera nazionale della piccola e media editoria che si tiene come ogni anno a Roma, denominata &amp;ldquo;Più libri più liberi&amp;rdquo; ed ho avuto il piacere di assistere ad una tavola rotonda con ospiti il direttore di Repubblica Maurizio Molinari e lo scrittore e divulgatore Corrado Augias.
Molinari ha presentato il suo ultimo libro &amp;ldquo;Mediterraneo conteso&amp;rdquo;, interrogandosi sugli scenari geopolitici odierni, sulle mosse delle geopotenze per la conquista dell&amp;rsquo;egemonia del presente/futuro e sull&amp;rsquo;importanza che riveste il controllo del &amp;ldquo;Mare nostrum&amp;rdquo; in tal senso.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Napoleon</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/napoleon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/napoleon/</guid>
      <description>Warning [SPOILER ALERT]
I recently saw Ridley Scott&amp;rsquo;s new film, Napoleon, a short cinematic reconstruction of the rise and fall of Napoleon Bonaparte.
Napoleon is played by Joaquin Phoenix, an outstanding actor in every performance. Even if here in my opinion a little subdued.
The film retraces some of the most important battles of Bonaparte&amp;rsquo;s career and is centered on the love story with his Josephine. There are some scenes that are a little rough in my opinion, not worthy of Ridley Scott (the cannons against the Egyptian pyramids?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NAZ, rise and fall of Prince Naseem Hamed</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/naz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/naz/</guid>
      <description>At the suggestion of a friend of mine, I saw a short documentary on the boxing career of Prince Naseem Hamed.
&amp;ldquo;Naz&amp;rdquo; was certainly one of the most influential boxers of the late 90s and early 2000s and one of the greatest featherweights in history. He had very powerful and precise strikes for a featherweight and an engaging, very show-oriented in-ring style.
I have always had the idea that his successful career was made possible by having to face weak opponents and by the need to create a character who could bring prestige to the minor categories of boxing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NBA In-Season Tournament</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/nba-inseason/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/nba-inseason/</guid>
      <description>A tournament within the already exhausting NBA season.
It&amp;rsquo;s called the NBA In-Season Tournament which this week will see the final round and the winner of the first edition.
The prize will be a cash budget to be distributed to the various players and the new trophy, NBA Cup (a kind of National Cup?).
Luckily the matches of this new tournament will also be valid for the regular season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street of Philadelphia</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/street-of-philadelphia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/street-of-philadelphia/</guid>
      <description>Some days ago like every year, December 1st, was International AIDS Day.
The AIDS syndrome appeared forcefully in the 1980s and is still a very important and widespread disease today.
There is very little communication now on this topic but it is good to remember that 40 years later, medicine has made important progress and today people with the HIV virus live an almost normal life. Yes, because the HIV virus leads to AIDS syndrome only if patients do not adequately follow a therapeutic path and do not take drugs that contain the virus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The great dictator - Final speech</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/great-dictator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/great-dictator/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, but I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be an emperor That&amp;rsquo;s not my business I don&amp;rsquo;t want to rule or conquer anyone I should like to help everyone if possible Jew, Gentile, Black Man, White We all want to help one another, human beings are like that We want to live by each other&amp;rsquo;s happiness, not by each other&amp;rsquo;s misery We don&amp;rsquo;t want to hate and despise one another
And this world has room for everyone, and the good Earth is rich and can provide for everyone The way of life can be free and beautiful, but we have lost the way Greed has posioned men&amp;rsquo;s souls, has barricaded the world with hate, has goose-stepped us into misery and bloodshed We have developed speed, but we have shut ourselves in Machinery that gives us abundance has left us in want</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The importance of reading books</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>At the basis of a simple and natural understanding of oneself, which is I believe the definition of happiness (albeit intermittently), is the discovery of what is not so obvious through reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The riddle</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/theriddle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/theriddle/</guid>
      <description>Near a tree by a river there&amp;rsquo;s a hole in the ground.
Where an old man a baron goes around and around.
And his mind is a beacon in the veil of the night.
For a strange kind of fashion there&amp;rsquo;s a wrong and a right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The unbearable lightness of being REM</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/all-the-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/all-the-way/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a reason why I like REM&amp;rsquo;s songs, because they are ethereal and have a dreamlike dimension for me.
One big regret is never having seen them live. They&amp;rsquo;re certainly not the type to do a nostalgic reunion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tyson vs Douglas</title>
      <link>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/tyson-douglas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hifly81.github.io/posts/tyson-douglas/</guid>
      <description>My father was a great boxing fan and inevitably passed this passion on to me too.
I saw many matches with him, especially those of Carlos Monzon and Marvin &amp;ldquo;The Marvelous&amp;rdquo; Hagler.
In the second half of the 80s the heavyweight scene was monopolized by a boy from the suburbs of New York, who became the youngest heavyweight champion of the world, Mike &amp;ldquo;Iron&amp;rdquo; Tyson, shocking the world with instant KOs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
